in this tutorial we're going to look at
在本教程中，我们将研究
扭曲机制非常
in this tutorial we're going to look at
the twisting mechanism which is a very
令人愉悦的机制
页面打开机制时的操作
the twisting mechanism which is a very
pleasing mechanism it has a very unusual
它是由两个V组成的
文件何时互相指向
pleasing mechanism it has a very unusual
action as the page opens the mechanism
底座是平的，它们平躺，然后
您可以在顶部构建许多东西
action as the page opens the mechanism
twists around it's it's made of two V
因此，这里有一个打开的例子
人物转过身来
twists around it's it's made of two V
files pointing at each other when when
本质上，你有六架飞机，所以
每个顶部两个，底部每个
files pointing at each other when when
the base is flat they lie flat and then
V折，然后有两个
平行折叠在顶部，然后
the base is flat they lie flat and then
you can build a number of things on top
您可以构建的沟渠
封闭的沟渠
you can build a number of things on top
of it so here is an example as it opens
关闭，您显然有一个
平行折叠下方的顶部
of it so here is an example as it opens
the figure twists around and opens up in
顶部有两个，底部有两个
V折所在的位置，然后在
the figure twists around and opens up in
essence you've got six planes so there's
V形折叠还有另外两个
你有四个那里两个那里六个，
essence you've got six planes so there's
two on each top and bottom on each of
然后那里有七个沟渠
建筑，这实际上并没有
two on each top and bottom on each of
the V folds and then it's got two on the
内置在任何沟渠中
扩展平原，使这些
the V folds and then it's got two on the
parallel folds on top and then the
头和手臂从一架飞机上下来
这是一个，然后这些
parallel folds on top and then the
gullies that you can build into the
从另外两个开始，所以它正在使用
他们的四个飞机
gullies that you can build into the
gullies that that close as the base
您需要一个底纸，这是底纸
床单折成半折
gullies that that close as the base
closes you've got one obviously in the
彻底，然后你需要另一个
关于我的另一件大事
closes you've got one obviously in the
top underneath the parallel fold you've
实际上已经在
中间那种方式真的折叠
top underneath the parallel fold you've
got two under top and two on the bottom
彻底地，我在每个位置都添加了一个折痕
结束粘贴标签，然后您想要
got two under top and two on the bottom
where the V folds are and then within
另一个折痕在中间
它使您纵向折叠它使
where the V folds are and then within
the v-folds you've got another two so
确定这次确保那两个
中央折痕相互对齐
the v-folds you've got another two so
you've got four there two there six and
这样您就知道一切都会正常进行
很好，所以有
you've got four there two there six and
then one there so seven gullies to
把它折起来再折起来
真的很彻底，所以你有
then one there so seven gullies to
building and this one hasn't actually
现在有了十字形，您实际上需要
这样又有两个折痕
building and this one hasn't actually
built into any of the gullies it's just
所以一种方法是将其折叠并
带上折痕线，以便您可以做
built into any of the gullies it's just
extending the plains so that these the
这样，但这是一种方法
并将它折回去，这样另一个
extending the plains so that these the
head and arm that's coming off one plane
其他方式，如果您发现真的
很难用卡带盒
head and arm that's coming off one plane
this is coming off one and then these
因此，产生45度平方的原因
学位以及您的目标
this is coming off one and then these
are coming off two others so it's using
是8个角度，它们都将是
45度，这样您就可以放下
are coming off two others so it's using
four of their planes
中央折痕用
铅笔或用你的酒吧得分
you need a base sheet here's the base
有一个，然后你可以做同样的
在另一边，那就是
you need a base sheet here's the base
sheet folded in half crease really
我们想要的线我们现在不会折叠
您只需将其折叠即可
sheet folded in half crease really
thoroughly and then you need another
通过确保这些来检查它
这些折痕排成一列，看上去
thoroughly and then you need another
another piece about this big I've
早期所以有点棘手，这是一个
有点棘手，但这就是你的结局
another piece about this big I've
actually already creased it in the
与折痕都使
星形，现在您应该能够
actually already creased it in the
middle that way folded it really
像这样推动它，这就是
最终形成这些形状
middle that way folded it really
thoroughly I've added a a crease at each
两个中央折痕应齐平
彼此
thoroughly I've added a a crease at each
end for gluing tags and then you want
理想情况下，有一点余地
但
end for gluing tags and then you want
another crease going down the middle of
他们彼此之间更多的闪光
更好，然后有时候你可以
another crease going down the middle of
it so you fold it lengthwise so make
删掉最后一点，因为
很多卡都聚在一起
it so you fold it lengthwise so make
sure this time make sure those two
在那里，它有点厚
所以只是使其工作更多一点
sure this time make sure those two
central creases line up with each other
顺利，您可以将其切断，这样
这就是你最终得到的形状
central creases line up with each other
so that you know it's all going to work
现在您只希望每个末端都有一个标签
因此在此结束时做一个标签
so that you know it's all going to work
nicely so there's the there's that
然后再减少一点
而不是仅仅沿着
nicely so there's the there's that
crease fold it back on it so fold it
折痕那里再剪一点
否则你会得到一点
crease fold it back on it so fold it
really thoroughly so you've got you've
在这里可能会缠住其他东西，所以
你只是把它切断到
really thoroughly so you've got you've
got a cross shape now you actually need
角落把它拿走，所以你有一个
将标签从一端粘上，然后
got a cross shape now you actually need
two more creases going across like this
关键是其他粘合
选项卡必须与对角线相反，不在
two more creases going across like this
so one way is to just fold it across and
相同的一面，这是第二个
胶合时间，这就是你想要的形状
so one way is to just fold it across and
bring the creasing lines so you can do
最后，现在你要
把胶水我需要四个中央
bring the creasing lines so you can do
it like that but that's one way of doing
面板，所有这些都将粘在上面
中央折痕对齐
it like that but that's one way of doing
it and fold that back on it so the other
底部中央折痕
而这四个粘在一起，你可以
it and fold that back on it so the other
other ways if you find that really
整个东西都可以粘在一起
所以你可以把胶水涂在这四个
other ways if you find that really
difficult you can use a cassette square
同时确保我们
不要错过我们折叠的胶水
difficult you can use a cassette square
so the causes of the set square of 45
进入该位置使其更容易
使胶水达到折痕而不是
so the causes of the set square of 45
degrees and what you're aiming for here
超越
对，所以把它打开平整
degrees and what you're aiming for here
is 8 angles and they're all going to be
中央折痕与中央折痕
在底座上，然后粘在上面
is 8 angles and they're all going to be
45 degrees so you can just put that down
将那些胶粘平放，然后关闭
它和这两个部分
45 degrees so you can just put that down
that central crease mark it with a
应该举起来，这样在一起
在那里，您可以看到两种V字体
that central crease mark it with a
pencil or score it with your bar oh so
一起打开和关闭它
所以现在你要贴另一个
pencil or score it with your bar oh so
there's one and then you can do the same
跨越这两个让我们尝试
有点红色
there's one and then you can do the same
on the other side so that's the that's
我们不希望它超出这个范围
我们已经附上了一块，所以瞄准
on the other side so that's the that's
the line we want we won't fold it so now
或多或少都一样，然后
不得短于距离
the line we want we won't fold it so now
you just fold it along there you can
在这两个折痕之间
短于整个机制就不能
you just fold it along there you can
check it by just making sure that these
打开时间越长
它会站立得越多，所以我们开始
check it by just making sure that these
these creases line up and they look the
只是将其折叠在中间，这样您就可以
像中间一样折皱
these creases line up and they look the
early so that is a bit tricky it is a
那然后这将适合
这样，如果我们看看这个
early so that is a bit tricky it is a
bit tricky but so that is you end up
关于，我们只说一个
两端各分开1厘米
bit tricky but so that is you end up
with the with the creases all making a
半
保持对称，我们可以采取
with the with the creases all making a
star shape and now you should be able to
像这样的一块
粘在这个位置，所以这些
star shape and now you should be able to
push it in like that so this is the
标签，他们可以在最上面
如果它们可见或您可以隐藏
push it in like that so this is the
shape you end up with and these these
他们在下面，所以我们把它们
下
shape you end up with and these these
two central creases should be flush with
好，确保边缘与
油脂，然后那个去那里
two central creases should be flush with
each other
您可以关闭基座并使其全部
有点大，所以就足够了
each other
ideally there is a little bit of leeway
它与假人一起使用的方式，因此您可以
虚拟，然后您会看到尺寸
ideally there is a little bit of leeway
but
你会看到你所需要的成长
改变，所以这是假人
but
more flash they are with each other the
扭曲的机制，所以这是小红
骑行兜帽
more flash they are with each other the
better and then sometimes you can just
布鲁斯·福斯特（Bruce Foster）和我们的造纸工程
打开这个，这是扭曲的
better and then sometimes you can just
cut out that final point because there's
机制，他被狼吞噬了
躲在树后面
cut out that final point because there's
a whole lot of cards all come together
大概这样看就可以了
它移动时它如何扭曲打开
a whole lot of cards all come together
there and it makes it a little bit thick
无论如何扩展了不同的飞机
那就是下一个是
there and it makes it a little bit thick
so just to make it work a little more
圣诞节前的晚上，Robertsóbuda
在这个襟翼下，
so just to make it work a little more
smoothly you can just cut that it off so
扭曲的惊人例子
机制，谁是开放的，他是
smoothly you can just cut that it off so
this is the shape you've ended up with
得到了全部六架飞机或至少五架飞机
这些已经扩展了这些
this is the shape you've ended up with
now you only want one tab on each end
这些切口，使襟翼打开，
关闭，所以您可以看到整个团伙
now you only want one tab on each end
and so make a tab on this end up here
鹿驯鹿，他们都把我
旋转旋转动作非常好
and so make a tab on this end up here
and just cut it back a bit further
例子，然后下一个是
Nick Dench创作的胡桃夹子填补了
and just cut it back a bit further
rather than just cutting along the the
他使用了一个不寻常的变化
扭转机制提高
rather than just cutting along the the
crease there cut it back a bit bit more
圣诞树，所以这实际上是
实心形状被提升而不是
crease there cut it back a bit bit more
otherwise you'll end up with a point
只是几架飞机，所以你可以看到一个
修女，你可以看到看到的v形折叠
otherwise you'll end up with a point
here which might snag on other things so
再次下降在一起
在圣诞树上捧着
here which might snag on other things so
you just cut that off to the to the
旋转，所以我想要的最后一个
告诉你我的丛林弹出书，
you just cut that off to the to the
corner take it off there so you've got a
这有一个非常有趣的变化
所以在这里，在这种情况下
corner take it off there so you've got a
gluing tab off one end there and then
翻页时，v形折叠不会翻盖
平他们站起来，这是一块
gluing tab off one end there and then
the crucial thing is the other gluing
在顶部举起
最终变得平坦而不是很高
the crucial thing is the other gluing
tab must be diagonally opposite not on
对，你知道向上平行折叠
所以它在这两个之间折叠
tab must be diagonally opposite not on
the same side so here's the second
V是这样的一个很好的例子
这就是扭曲机制
the same side so here's the second
gluing time this is the shape you want
所有这些都在我的书中有更详细的解释
弹出式设计和纸张力学
gluing time this is the shape you want
to end up with and now you're going to
您